(Sheldon:)There are myriad weapons,
vehicles and strategies to master...
...not to mention an intricate back-story.
[EXPLOSION ON TV]
Oh, cool!
Whose head did I just blow off?
(Sheldon:)Mine.
(Penny:)Okay, I got this. Lock and load, boys.
(Leonard:)It's the only way we can play teams.
(Sheldon:)Whoever's her partner will be hamstrung
by her lack of experience, not to mention...
[EXPLOSION ON TV]
Ha-ha! There goes your head again.
Okay, it's not good sportsmanship
to shoot somebody who's just re-spawned.
(Sheldon:)You need to give them a chance to...
Now, come on.
[EXPLOSION ON TV]
(Sheldon:)Raj, Raj, she's got me cornered.
Cover me.
(Penny:)Cover this, suckers.
[CHUCKLING]
(Leonard:)Penny, you are on fire.
Yeah, and so is Sheldon.
[LAUGHING]
(Sheldon:)Okay, that's it.
I don't know how, but she is cheating.
No one can be that attractive
and this skilled at a video game.
(Penny:)Wait, Sheldon, come back.
You forgot something.
(Penny:)What?
(Penny:)This plasma grenade.
[EXPLOSION ON TV]
(Penny:)Ha! Look, it's raining you.